Bennet, William Stiles; Papers apap226
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Political Materials and Oversized Items, 1888-1951; Undated; 4; 2.09 cubic ft.
  - Newburgh Tax Commission, Report of Financial Condition and Operations, Budgetary Control and Financial Reporting and the Accounting Methods and Procedures of the City of Newburgh, NY, Undated (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 27)
  - Oral History of William Stiles Bennet, Undated (Oversized 3)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 28)
  - Political Memorabilia, 1904-1914; 1921-1938 (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 29)
  - Political Pamphlets and Clips, 1932-1934; Undated (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 30)
  - Printed Speeches, 1910-1916; 1925; 1934; Undated (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook, 1944-1945 (Oversized 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1915-1917 (Oversized 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1902-1904 (Oversized 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1901-1902 (Oversized 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1898-1900 (Oversized 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1900-1901 (Box 5 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items))
  - Undated MSS Speeches (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 32-33)
  - Vice Presidential Campaign, Oregon Correspondence, 1936 (Box 11 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 34)
  - Vice Presidential Campaign, 1936 (Box 12 (4-Political Materials and Oversized Items), Folder 1-3)